Guide to the Yonkers Police Department Records 1867-1907 MS 296
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Yonkers Police Blotters, 1867 - 1907
  - Blotter 1897, 13 October 1897 - 2 November 1897 (Offsite-volume 270)
  - Blotter 1897, 2 November 1897 - 20 November 1897 (Offsite-volume 271)
  - Blotter 1897, 20 November 1897 - 14 December 1897 (Offsite-volume 272)
  - Blotter 1897-1898, 14 December 1897 - 5 January 1898 (Offsite-volume 273)
  - Blotter 1898, 5 January 1898 - 25 January 1898 (Offsite-volume 274)
  - Blotter 1898, 25 January 1898 - 15 February 1898 (Offsite-volume 275)
  - Blotter 1898, 15 February 1898 - 6 March 1898 (Offsite-volume 276)
  - Blotter 1898, 6 March 1898 - 25 March 1898 (Offsite-volume 277)
  - Blotter 1898, 25 March 1898 - 13 April 1898 (Offsite-volume 278)
  - Blotter 1898, 13 April 1898 - 1 May 1898 (Offsite-volume 279)
  - Blotter 1898, 1 May 1898 - 19 May 1898 (Offsite-volume 280)
  - Blotter 1898, 19 May 1898 - 7 June 1898 (Offsite-volume 281)
  - Blotter 1898, 7 June 1898 - 26 June 1898 (Offsite-volume 282)
  - Blotter 1898, 26 June 1898 - 14 July 1898 (Offsite-volume 283)
  - Blotter 1898, 26 June 1898 - 14 July 1898 (Offsite-volume 283)
  - Blotter 1898, 14 July 1898 - 2 August 1898 (Offsite-volume 284)
  - Blotter 1898, 2 August 1898 - 20 August 1898 (Offsite-volume 285)
  - Blotter 1898, 20 August 1898 - 10 September 1898 (Offsite-volume 286)
  - Blotter 1898, 10 September 1898 - 30 September 1898 (Offsite-volume 287)
  - Blotter 1898, 1 October 1898 - 20 October 1898 (Offsite-volume 288)
  - Blotter 1898, 20 October 1898 - 7 November 1898 (Offsite-volume 289)
  - Blotter 1898, 7 November 1898 - 28 November 1898 (Offsite-volume 290)
  - Blotter 1898, 28 November 1898 - 17 December 1898 (Offsite-volume 291)
  - Blotter 1898-1899, 17 December 1898 - 6 January 1899 (Offsite-volume 292)
  - Blotter 1899, 7 January 1899 - 27 January 1899 (Offsite-volume 293)
  - Blotter 1899, 27 January 1899 - 16 February 1899 (Offsite-volume 294)
  - Blotter 1899, 16 February 1899 - 5 March 1899 (Offsite-volume 295)
  - Blotter 1899, 5 March 1899 - 23 March 1899 (Offsite-volume 296)
  - Blotter 1899, 23 March 1899 - 9 April 1899 (Offsite-volume 297)
  - Blotter 1899, 9 April 1899 - 26 April 1899 (Offsite-volume 298)
  - Blotter 1899, 26 April 1899 - 15 May 1899 (Offsite-volume 299)
  - Blotter 1899, 15 May 1899 - 4 June 1899 (Offsite-volume 300)
  - Blotter 1899, 4 June 1899 - 23 June 1899 (Offsite-volume 301)
  - Blotter 1899, 23 June 1899 - 12 July 1899 (Offsite-volume 302)
  - Blotter 1899, 12 July 1899 - 31 July 1899 (Offsite-volume 303)
  - Blotter 1899, 31 July 1899 - 18 August 1899 (Offsite-volume 304)
  - Blotter 1899, 18 August 1899 - 8 September 1899 (Offsite-volume 305)
  - Blotter 1899, 8 September 1899 - 28 September 1899 (Offsite-volume 306)
  - Blotter 1899, 28 September 1899 - 9 October 1899 (Offsite-volume 307)
  - Blotter 1899, 9 October 1899 - 6 November 1899 (Offsite-volume 308)
  - Blotter 1899, 6 November 1899 - 27 November 1899 (Offsite-volume 309)
  - Blotter 1899, 27 November 1899 - 17 December 1899 (Offsite-volume 310)
  - Blotter 1899-1900, 17 December 1899 - 6 January 1900 (Offsite-volume 311)
  - Blotter 1900, 6 January 1900 - 27 January 1900 (Offsite-volume 312)
  - Blotter 1900, 27 January 1900 - 16 February 1900 (Offsite-volume 313)
  - Blotter 1900, 16 February 1900 - 8 March 1900 (Offsite-volume 314)
  - Blotter 1900, 8 March 1900 - 29 March 1900 (Offsite-volume 315)
  - Blotter 1900, 29 March 1900 - 19 April 1900 (Offsite-volume 316)
  - Blotter 1900, 19 April 1900 - 10 May 1900 (Offsite-volume 317)
  - Blotter 1900, 10 May 1900 - 30 May 1900 (Offsite-volume 318)
  - Blotter 1900, 30 May 1900 - 21 June 1900 (Offsite-volume 319)
  - Blotter 1900, 21 June 1900 - 12 July 1900 (Offsite-volume 320)
  - Blotter 1900, 12 July 1900 - 2 August 1900 (Offsite-volume 321)
  - Blotter 1900, 2 August 1900 - 22 August 1900 (Offsite-volume 322)
  - Blotter 1900, 22 August 1900 - 12 September 1900 (Offsite-volume 323)
  - Blotter 1900, 12 September 1900 - 4 October 1900 (Offsite-volume 324)
  - Blotter 1900, 4 October 1900 - 27 October 1900 (Offsite-volume 325)
  - Blotter 1900, 27 October 1900 - 17 November 1900 (Offsite-volume 326)
  - Blotter 1900, 17 November 1900 - 9 December 1900 (Offsite-volume 327)
  - Blotter 1900, 9 December 1900 - 30 December 1900 (Offsite-volume 328)
  - Blotter 1900-1901, 30 December 1900 - 21 January 1901 (Offsite-volume 329)
  - Blotter 1901, 27 March 1901 - 17 April 1901 (Offsite-volume 330)
  - Blotter 1901, 17 April 1901 - 7 May 1901 (Offsite-volume 331)
  - Blotter 1901, 7 May 1901 - 28 May 1901 (Offsite-volume 332)
  - Blotter 1901, 28 May 1901 - 16 June 1901 (Offsite-volume 333)
  - Blotter 1901, 16 June 1901 - 7 July 1901 (Offsite-volume 334)
  - Blotter 1901, 7 July 1901 - 28 July 1901 (Offsite-volume 335)
  - Blotter 1901, 28 July 1901 - 18 August 1901 (Offsite-volume 336)
  - Blotter 1901, 20 August 1901 - 11 September 1901 (Offsite-volume 337)
  - Blotter 1901, 11 September 1901 - 3 October 1901 (Offsite-volume 338)
  - Blotter 1901, 3 October 1901 - 24 October 1901 (Offsite-volume 339)
  - Blotter 1901, 8 December 1901 - 29 December 1901 (Offsite-volume 340)
  - Blotter 1901-1902, 29 December 1901 - 17 January 1902 (Offsite-volume 341)
  - Blotter 1902, 17 January 1902 - 6 February 1902 (Offsite-volume 342)
  - Blotter 1902, 6 February 1902 - 26 February 1902 (Offsite-volume 343)
  - Blotter 1902, 18 March 1902 - 7 April 1902 (Offsite-volume 344)
  - Blotter 1902, 7 April 1902 - 27 April 1902 (Offsite-volume 345)
  - Blotter 1902, 27 April 1902 - 15 May 1902 (Offsite-volume 346)
  - Blotter 1902, 4 June 1902 - 22 June 1902 (Offsite-volume 347)
  - Blotter 1902, 22 June 1902 - 11 July 1902 (Offsite-volume 348)
  - Blotter 1902, 11 July 1902 - 29 July 1902 (Offsite-volume 349)
  - Blotter 1902, 29 July 1902 - 17 August 1902 (Offsite-volume 350)
  - Blotter 1902, 17 August 1902 - 5 September 1902 (Offsite-volume 351)
  - Blotter 1902, 5 September 1902 - 23 September 1902 (Offsite-volume 352)
  - Blotter 1902, 23 September 1902 - 12 October 1902 (Offsite-volume 353)
  - Blotter 1902, 8 December 1902 - 26 December 1902 (Offsite-volume 354)
  - Blotter 1902-1903, 26 December 1902 - 14 January 1903 (Offsite-volume 355)
  - Blotter 1903, 31 January 1903 - 18 February 1903 (Offsite-volume 356)
  - Blotter 1903, 9 March 1903 - 27 March 1903 (Offsite-volume 357)
  - Blotter 1903, 27 March 1903 - 14 April 1903 (Offsite-volume 358)
  - Blotter 1903, 22 May 1903 - 9 June 1903 (Offsite-volume 359)
  - Blotter 1903, 9 June 1903 - 28 June 1903 (Offsite-volume 360)
  - Blotter 1903, 17 July 1903 - 4 August 1903 (Offsite-volume 361)
  - Blotter 1903, 4 August 1903 - 23 August 1903 (Offsite-volume 362)
  - Blotter 1903, 26 November 1903 - 14 December 1903 (Offsite-volume 363)
  - Blotter 1904, 21 January 1904 - 9 February 1904 (Offsite-volume 364)
  - Blotter 1904, 1 January 1904 - 20 January 1904 (Offsite-volume 365)
  - Blotter 1904, 4 April 1904 - 27 April 1904 (Offsite-volume 366)
  - Blotter 1904, 27 April 1904 - 10 May 1904 (Offsite-volume 367)
  - Blotter 1904, 14 June 1904 - 21 July 1904 (Offsite-volume 368)
  - Blotter 1904, 28 May 1904 - 14 June 1904 (Offsite-volume 369)
  - Blotter 1904, 4 August 1904 - 27 August 1904 (Offsite-volume 370)
  - Blotter 1904, 28 August 1904 - 14 September 1904 (Offsite-volume 371)
  - Blotter 1904, 15 September 1904 - 5 October 1904 (Offsite-volume 372)
  - Blotter 1904, 5 October 1904 - 23 October 1904 (Offsite-volume 373)
  - Blotter 1904, 1 December 1904 - 21 December 1904 (Offsite-volume 374)
  - Blotter 1904-1905, 21 December 1904 - 10 January 1905 (Offsite-volume 375)
  - Blotter 1905, 11 January 1905 - 1 February 1905 (Offsite-volume 376)
  - Blotter 1905, 1 February 1905 - 23 February 1905 (Offsite-volume 377)
  - Blotter 1905, 23 February 1905 - 16 March 1905 (Offsite-volume 378)
  - Blotter 1905, 25 April 1905 - 14 May 1905 (Offsite-volume 379)
  - Blotter 1905, 14 May 1905 - 1 June 1905 (Offsite-volume 380)
  - Blotter 1905, 10 July 1905 - 30 July 1905 (Offsite-volume 381)
  - Blotter 1905, 30 July 1905 - 17 August 1905 (Offsite-volume 382)
  - Blotter 1905, 18 August 1905 - 7 September 1905 (Offsite-volume 383)
  - Blotter 1905, 7 September 1905 - 26 September 1905 (Offsite-volume 384)
  - Blotter 1905, 13 October 1905 - 26 October 1905 (Offsite-volume 385)
  - Blotter 1905, 26 November 1905 - 9 December 1905 (Offsite-volume 386)
  - Blotter 1905, 9 December 1905 - 24 December 1905 (Offsite-volume 387)
  - Blotter 1905-1906, 24 December 1905 - 8 January 1906 (Offsite-volume 388)
  - Blotter 1906, 24 January 1906 - 8 February 1906 (Offsite-volume 389)
  - Blotter 1906, 12 March 1906 - 28 March 1906 (Offsite-volume 390)
  - Blotter 1906, 13 April 1906 - 29 April 1906 (Offsite-volume 391)
  - Blotter 1906, 16 June 1906 - 2 July 1906 (Offsite-volume 392)
  - Blotter 1906, 2 August 1906 - 17 August 1906 (Offsite-volume 393)
  - Blotter 1906, 17 August 1906 - 2 September 1906 (Offsite-volume 394)
  - Blotter 1906, 2 September 1906 - 18 September 1906 (Offsite-volume 395)
  - Blotter 1906, 18 September 1906 - 4 October 1906 (Offsite-volume 396)
  - Blotter 1906, 20 October 1906 - 4 November 1906 (Offsite-volume 397)
  - Blotter 1906, 4 November 1906 - 20 November 1906 (Offsite-volume 398)
  - Blotter 1906, 20 November 1906 - 3 December 1906 (Offsite-volume 399)
  - Blotter 1906, 3 December 1906 - 21 December 1906 (Offsite-volume 400)
  - Blotter 1906-1907, 21 December 1906 - 6 January 1907 (Offsite-volume 401)
  - Blotter 1933-1935 (includes mug shots), 1933 January 21 - 1936 August 26 (Offsite-volume 402)
    Note
    A few loose documents and mug shots have been removed and placed in a separate envelope housed with this volume.
- Series II: Minute Books and Force Book
  - YPD Office of the Secretary, Board of Police -- Minutes and Resolutions, 1841 - 1904 (Offsite-volume 403)
  - YPD Board of Police -- Minutes and Resolutions, 20 April 1881 - 23 December 1891 (Offsite-volume 404)
  - YPD Board of Police -- Minutes and Resolutions, 13 January 1892 - 14 July 1903 (Offsite-volume 405)
  - YPD Force Book, circa 1880's - 1904 (Offsite-volume 406)